[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ upbeat music playing]
EPISODE 5
[cell phone vibrating]
Hmm?
Good morning, Mr. Choi.
Good morning.
[Isoo] What made you call so early?
I booked a consultation for you.
[sighs] I told you I don't like shrinks.
What if I get hypnotized again
and do something? I'm not going.
I'm worried about you.
Why do you worry so much? Huh?
Didn't you see me catch those hitmen?
Nothing bad happened.
Just listen to me.
Ignoring it won't make it go away.
You get yourself checked out first.
Ignoring indigestion won't make it better.
[sighs in exasperation]
Will you go if I go?
Of course. You go first, then I'll go.
I have to go to work now. Bye.
[line disconnects]
[sighs in exasperation]
[sets down phone]
[inhales]
[exhales deeply]
[elevator dings]
[digital beep]
[exhales softly]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[audio distorts]
[muffled metallic clinking]
[high-pitched tone droning]
[groans]
[thud]
[slow heartbeats]
[groans]
-[elevator clunks]
-[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[metallic clinking intensifies]
[high-pitched ringing intensifies]
[panting]
[audio normalizes]
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
[inhales]
[elevator dings]
[continues panting]
[♪ music fades]
ROSEBUD HOTEL
-[woman] I'm so excited!
-[chuckles]
[♪ quirky music playing]
-Welcome.
-Hello.
-We made a reservation.
-Yes, we did.
May I have your name?
Lee Gwanghui.
-Lee Gwanghui?
-[keyboard clacking]
-Why are you so cute today?
-Because today's a special day.
Really? Oh...
I'm sorry, but I can't seem
to find your reservation.
What? Uh...
Then please try "Oh Gyeonghwa."
-Please.
-Oh Gyeonghwa.
Even her name's pretty.
[Gyeonghwa giggles]
-[keyboard clacking]
-[couple chattering indistinctly]
I'm sorry,
but I can't find your reservation.
-What?
-What's going on, babe?
That can't be right.
I'm sure I made a reservation. I...
STYLE
::cue()
I think I canceled to get
a lower rate and never rebooked.
Ah. Forget it. I'm leaving.
Wait, hold on.
So...
Could you perhaps save me?
I mean,
do you have any rooms left?
On White Day? As if.
One moment, please.
Everyone's walking around with candy.
I assumed mine was in the room.
-I really hope you have a room.
-Yes, we have one.
You do? We'll take it.
The last room on the seventh floor.
-Thank you. They had a room.
-Thank you.
-You're so annoying!
-Come on.
At least make an effort.
[clicks tongue]
I wish you'd forget what happened earlier.
-I can't forget it.
-Babe.
It's our one-year anniversary.
I wish you would.
I'll let it slide.
[groans affectionately] You're so cute.
[sighs] What am I supposed to do
if you're this cute even when you're mad?
I can't help it. I was born this way.
-I think I'm trapped.
-Me too.
-Please save us!
-Save us!
[elevator dings]
[Gwanghui] We're saved. [chuckles]
Wait, stop.
We can't just go like this.
-Here, hold this.
-Hmm?
[clears throat, spits]
[squeals]
[grunts]
-What are you doing?
-[panting]
My knees...
It's our anniversary today.
So your feet won't be touching
the ground all day.
Okay!
[♪ quirky music playing]
Now, where are we?
-Am I heavy?
-[continues panting] No.
You're light as a feather.
You should stop losing weight.
-You're lighter than a strand of hair.
-Okay.
-Now, where is our room?
-Over there.
Here we are!
-Okay!
-Here?
Yes, go on.
-Go on.
-Wait.
Hold it properly for it to...
-Try placing it carefully.
-Okay.
-[card reader beeps]
-It worked!
It worked!
-It worked.
Here we go!
-[exclaims excitedly]
-[panting]
-It's gorgeous.
-This room is amazing.
[shrieks] It's so beautiful!
-It's beautiful.
-Yes, it's so beautiful.
-[grunting]
-Isn't it great?
[♪ ominous sting]
-[exclaims]
-[squeals]
Babe, you're so manly!
Babe! Are you leaving?
[♪ ominous sting]
[screaming]
[sighs] They really shouldn't have
sent me all these.
Honestly.
Kyungjin.
Ooh, what's that?
It's for White Day.
-Thank you.
-Detective Park...
PARK JUNYOUNG
He took a day off on White Day?
That's very fishy.
What is?
My exceptional detective instincts
are kicking in.
That clueless Detective Park who only
listens to trot music is dating someone?
-He said he's meeting his mom.
-Right?
Who would date someone like him?
I'm sure he went to see his mom.
[♪ quirky music playing]
Is it White Day today?
-[Kim Suwon] Yes.
-[Byungsik exclaims]
I forgot last year, too.
Hey.
-Got any cash?
-Just pay by card.
I use my wife's card.
[Kim Suwon] Do I look like I have money?
Lend me 20,000 won.
Come on, just 20,000 won.
Just 20,000 won.
[whispers] He's surprisingly devoted.
[whispers] I heard
his wife is really scary.
[gasps]
What about you?
[sighs] I've already got my surprise
all planned out.
You're so diligent. A true romantic.
-Aren't you going to date, bro?
-Hey.
I prefer to meet people naturally.
Look at these. That's...
It's a new case.
We got a report of a body. Rosebud Hotel.
-Yes! You what?
-Today, I--
What about White Day?
The case comes first.
Okay, let's go.
-[Kyungjin] Come on.
-The case should come first.
[Kyungjin] But, bro, seriously...
STYLE
::cue()
We're with Gangha Police.
ROSEBUD HOTEL CONCIERGE
JEON YUJIN
Right.
I'm the general manager.
ROSEBUD HOTEL GENERAL MANAGER
YU JONGYEOL
Hello.
[♪ enthralling music playing]
Where's the scene?
In Room 709.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[♪ quirky music playing]
Detective Park.
What are you doing here?
I called him.
Why? It's his day off.
The case comes first.
Dr. Yoon?
Dr. Yoon from Forensic Pathology? Oh!
Gosh, Detective Jin.
Fancy meeting you here.
[Isoo] What are you doing here?
I have plans, obviously. [chuckles]
I was actually on my way out.
This is perfect timing.
-A body was found here.
-What?
-Come with us.
-But I...
You're here.
-[Dr. Yoon] Oh.
-Yeah.
You were here, too. [chuckles softly]
Hello, Dr. Yoon.
Dr. Yoon.
We've met before.
Oh, yes, Detective Joo.
[chuckles]
I look forward to working with you.
Likewise.
Please follow me.
Come on, let's go.
-Let's go.
-[clears throat] Yes, let's go.
So Dr. Yoon is his mom?
Did you see that? They were linking arms.
-They jumped apart in surprise.
-[giggles]
-What plans did they have at a hotel?
-[Kyungjin] Drumroll.
This is the place.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
It looks like she's been dead for a while.
It's been at least 12 hours.
It looks like she was stabbed.
-In three places.
-Right.
She was stabbed in three places,
but there's not much bleeding.
[sighs]
Bleeding can be minimal.
It depends where you were stabbed.
-I'll check during the autopsy.
-Okay.
Her phone.
[Kyungjin] I don't see the murder weapon.
-Get this to forensics.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Hello, sir.
-Detective Joo.
We can't find the murder weapon,
and there's little blood.
-I'll take a look.
-Okay.
-You stay here, Detective Park.
-Got it.
Do you know the victim?
Her name's Oh Minyeong. She a concierge.
Where is the person who found the body?
They're at the bar.
This way, please.
-What?
-Are you even human?
I am. I'm human.
I'm drinking because I'm human.
You're worse than an animal.
Don't talk that way.
Have some manners in a place like this.
-You're seriously saying that right now?
-Babe.
-Hello.
-Gosh, you startled me.
STYLE
::cue()
Aren't you Jin Isoo?
Yes, I am.
[shrieks excitedly]
Oh my god. You're so good-looking.
He's not that good-looking.
No one asked you, ugly.
[Gwanghui] Ugly?
You've got to be kidding me.
Can I get a photo with you?
-Why not?
-[Gyeonghwa] Thank you.
-Ugly, huh?
-I'll take it.
Thanks.
One, two, three.
[Gwanghui] Don't stand too close.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[squeals]
Oh, uh, is she your girlfriend?
Gosh, of course not.
We're police.
[Isoo] I'm here to work.
You found the body, didn't you?
Can you explain what happened?
We started dating on White Day last year.
So I made a reservation
for our one-year anniversary,
but there was a bit of a problem.
You were too cheap to book it.
You're really going to humiliate me
in front of other people?
I said it was a mistake.
And?
Ah, so our reservation was canceled,
but it turns out they had one room left.
They had a room left on White Day?
They would've been overbooked.
No, they had a room left.
So I carried my adorable baby
and walked down the hallway.
Yes, exactly.
It was straight out of a movie. [chuckles]
Since we're on the subject,
you were a little heavier
than you used to be.
-I almost threw my back out.
-You said I was as light as a feather.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hey, Mr. Ugly.
Let's focus here.
-Yes, Mr. Ugly.
-Right.
So we opened the door like this,
but then, some woman
was right there behind the bed,
like a ghost.
With her eyes wide open.
So we just ran out of there.
Why leave out the part where
you threw me onto the bed? Embarrassed?
[scoffs] You're bent on making me
look like a coward, aren't you?
I told you, I was just startled.
Exactly. You ditch your girlfriend
when you're startled.
I just panicked for a second.
-Enough. I'm upset.
-And I'm humiliated!
Okay, focus.
Did you touch anything inside the room?
Or see anything strange?
No.
Nothing like that.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We may contact you again.
Okay.
[Isoo inhales sharply]
-He looks familiar.
-[Gyeonghwa] Bye.
You and I are over!
How many times must I apologize?
-Fine, blame me for being a coward.
-[Isoo sighs]
It's like watching a soap opera.
That's why I don't date.
Isn't it that you can't?
With this face?
[scoffs]
She's the narcissistic one.
[whispers] She's unbelievable.
Just go. Don't let my screaming stop you.
We've prepared a suite for you.
Please stay as long as you like.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
During your stay,
all hotel services, including
food and beverages, are complimentary.
-Including alcohol?
-Of course.
[gasps]
Get up.
You love free stuff, babe.
-[Gwanghui] Let's go.
-[Gyeonghwa giggles]
[sighs]
Jeez.
[scoffs]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I don't think I saw her
after 7:00 p.m. last night.
Right?
Yes, that's right.
Do you know anyone who might've had
a grudge against Ms. Oh Minyeong?
STYLE
::cue()
I'm not sure.
Did she have any trouble
with any guests at all?
[chuckles nervously]
[clears throat]
The hotel was all red and glossy,
but why is the back of house like this?
What about the staff?
They have rights too, don't they?
Wait.
-I'll be right back.
-Where are you going?
To canvass the area.
HOUSEKEEPING
[knocking]
-[housekeeper 1] Yes?
-Excuse me.
[♪ quirky music playing]
-Goodness.
-He's handsome.
-Aren't you the heir of Hansu Group?
-You're right.
Oh...
You ladies have a sharp eye.
Hear that? He called me a lady.
-It was me.
-No, it was me, silly.
What's a chaebol heir doing
all the way down here?
I'm in charge of Ms. Oh Minyeong's case.
-Ah...
-"In charge of"?
He's a detective.
He rammed a helicopter
into a car last year.
Yes, that was me.
-[chuckles] I think I saw that, too.
-[housekeeper 1] Right?
Excuse me.
Did Minyeong really die?
Yes, so I was wondering if I could get
some help from you lovely ladies.
Gosh, you keep calling us ladies
and flattering us like that.
Ow! You're pretty strong.
Try working here for three months,
you'll bulk right up.
We're all wearing matching outfits.
-You're right.
-Me too.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Detective Joo.
This is Ms. Oh Minyeong's shift log.
You should take a look at this.
[housekeeper 1] Minyeong?
Men just wouldn't leave her alone.
She's gorgeous.
Being pretty isn't easy. I would know.
I was quite the catch back in the day.
-You're still beautiful.
-[scoffs playfully]
Honestly, you have good taste.
[chuckles]
I think some of the staff
asked her out as well.
-[housekeeper 1] Really?
-Yeah.
Have you seen anyone suspicious lately?
-Anyone suspicious?
-Were there any?
[murmuring quietly]
Ah!
-Room 701.
-The ugly guy?
-Yes.
-Room 701?
I heard he's a chaebol heir.
He's been in the suite for three weeks.
And?
He kept calling for Minyeong,
saying he had requests to make.
[housekeeper 2] That's right.
He stared at her in this creepy way
and followed her around.
Right.
That funny-looking man.
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
Funny-looking?
He called for her multiple times a day.
REMARKS
ATTENDED TO ROOM 701
Who is the guest in Room 701?
That guest is confidential,
so I can't say.
Do you have cameras on the seventh floor?
The camera on the seventh floor
-is off.
-Why?
It broke down two months ago,
but it hasn't been repaired yet.
A five-star hotel just left
a broken security camera?
That doesn't make sense to me.
[Jongyeol] Uh...
A maintenance report wasn't filed.
It was a mistake.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
You two meet with Ms. Oh's family
and break the news.
See what they have to say.
-Got it. Let's go.
-Got it.
[line connects, ringing]
[cell phone vibrating]
[♪ gritty blues-rock music playing]
SHADOW WITHOUT A TRACE
TRACK TO THE END
JEONG MINJAE DETECTIVE AGENCY
HYERA
[cell phone continues vibrating]
Hey, it's been a while.
Yeah. How's the business going?
It looks like word got around.
I've been swamped.
[chuckles] I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Rosebud Hotel.
It's a murder case, but the security
camera on the seventh floor is down.
I need you to use the backdoor
to find out when and how it went offline.
I told you I'm busy.
It'll take you 10 minutes.
Five minutes.
-Gopchang?
-Deal.
-I'll call you later.
-Okay.
-[line disconnects]
-[hurried footsteps approaching]
-[Isoo] Detective Joo!
-Yeah.
[in English] Big news!
-[in Korean] Did you learn something?
-Of course.
There's a suspect
in the seventh-floor suite.
Yeah, he kept calling for Ms. Oh.
Let's go meet him.
Let's go.
Chunsik?
Oh.
Isoo!
KANG CHUNSIK
SOLE HEIR OF CHUNSIK FOOD
-"Isoo"?
-[Isoo] Yeah.
This is Kang Chunsik,
the sole heir of Chunsik Food.
[softly] Oh.
[♪ gripping, dramatic music playing]
He looks old,
but he's two years younger than us.
He was born in 1994.
What a nice thing to say
first thing in the morning.
Morning, huh?
It's 5:00 p.m. Anyway, go inside.
-Why?
-Come inside.
What's going on?
[Isoo] Whoa...
Look at the state of this room.
THE PERSON I FELL FOR
AT FIRST SIGHT IS...
[Chunsik] Something sad
happened yesterday.
[Isoo] Something sad?
What was it? Tell me.
What do you know about love?
Forget it.
[scoffs]
You've been here three weeks.
Did you run away from home?
No, I just...
I just came.
Is it because of Ms. Oh Minyeong?
Why are you asking about Ms. Oh Minyeong?
Her shift log says
you kept calling for her.
Oh...
I had requests to make, but why...
Wait, who are you?
She's a detective.
Be straight with us. I'm a detective, too.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Then why did you keep calling for her?
Were you stalking her?
Stalking? What are you talking about?
[angrily] I wasn't!
[sighs softly]
I fell for her at first sight.
[♪ gentle jazz music playing]
Here is the vase you requested.
Do you need anything else?
[♪ music fades]
That's what people call stalking.
And your face already screams "suspect."
I'm not bad-looking.
Right?
Uh...
No comment.
[Isoo] Don't you look in the mirror?
I told you to work on your looks
if you want to date. Just look at you.
I am working on my looks.
Do you know how expensive my clinic is?
Excuse me, please tell us
what happened yesterday.
Yesterday...
I asked her out.
I couldn't hide my feelings anymore.
If she said yes,
today would be our anniversary.
We'd be a White Day couple.
[mumbles]
With that?
Hey, that's from that movie.
It was a whole thing 20 years ago.
[Chunsik] Come on.
I had the perfect plan.
I want to confess my feelings
to the person I love.
STYLE
::cue()
[chuckles] How can I help with that?
Uh...
I need flowers, balloons, and a cake.
What kind of cake would you like?
I'm not sure.
Um...
What flavor do you like, Ms. Oh?
I'm clueless about what women like.
[chuckles]
Our hotel is famous
for our chocolate cake.
Then please prepare that.
Of course.
[♪ gentle, pleasant music playing]
[inaudible conversation]
Then I'll take my leave now.
Hold on.
I need to rehearse.
Could you sit here for a moment?
Just for one minute.
[♪ music fades]
[chuckles softly]
Please, this way.
Please sit here.
Okay.
[♪ dreamy retro music playing]
[sharp exhale]
I HAVE FALLEN IN LOVE
I have fallen in love.
I've never felt this way before.
I'm feeling a little shy.
She came to me with the scent of flowers.
You must be wondering who she is.
[chuckles]
The person I fell for at first sight is...
It's you, Minyeong.
Minyeong.
I'm sorry. I have a boyfriend.
Minyeong...
-[♪ music fades]
-[door opens]
[♪ soft melancholy music playing]
Another one, please.
[sobbing]
One more.
[♪ music fades]
Just like that,
the love of my life left me.
What time did you call
Ms. Oh Minyeong here?
[♪ soft suspenseful music playing]
Around
seven o'clock?
What time did she leave?
About
Forty minutes later.
Did she report me?
I really didn't stalk her.
My feelings are sincere.
[sighs deeply]
Ms. Oh Minyeong has died.
What?
She was murdered last night.
Chunsik.
Mr. Kang.
-[Isoo] Chunsik.
-Wake up, Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang, wake up.
[Isoo] Hey, hey...
[Hyera sighs]
[sniffs]
This is alcohol.
-So it is.
-Isoo.
[coughs] You're lying, right?
Please tell me it's a lie.
It's a lie, right?
Come on, Detective.
What in the world is going on?
You're a detective, Isoo!
[sobbing]
Minyeong!
[sighs softly]
[Chunsik continues sobbing]
Stop crying!
STYLE
::cue()
Did Ms. Oh Minyeong have a boyfriend?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Uh...
I'm not sure.
I don't know either.
Did anyone stay in Room 709 last night?
No, Room 709 was unoccupied.
It was unoccupied?
Why did she go
to an unoccupied room alone?
[♪ music swells, fades]
[sobbing, ragged breathing]
Why did our daughter...
Why did she die?
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[Minyeong's dad] Who did this?
We're still investigating the matter.
[continues sobbing, breathing raggedly]
Did your daughter
have a boyfriend?
It did seem like
she was seeing someone lately.
She even received an expensive handbag.
I think it was one of the hotel staff.
Did her boyfriend kill her?
We don't know yet.
By any chance,
was there anyone
who might've had a grudge against her?
Our daughter was the sweetest girl!
There isn't anyone like that!
Can we take a look around her room?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
This has to be worth a fortune.
Oh.
This is a limited edition.
You can't buy this with money.
[♪ music swells, fades]
SEWON HOSPITAL
The name is Choi Jeonghun.
[receptionist] Please wait just a moment.
[♪ gentle melancholy music playing]
[monitor beeping steadily]
[♪ music fades]
[clears throat softly]
-Mr. Choi Jeonghun?
-Yes.
-You're all done with your tests.
-Okay.
We sent your biopsy for analysis,
so the results will take a few days.
Let's get you booked in.
All right.
These two dates are available.
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
ROOM 709
[Hyera] She went into
an unoccupied room and died.
Why?
[cell phone vibrating]
Hey.
That camera on the seventh floor
isn't broken. It was turned off.
STYLE
::cue()
It was blocked by the central server.
January 14, at 8:00 p.m.
MANUAL RECORDING STOP
Okay, thank you.
Someone manipulated the camera
and planned this murder?
REPORTING PARTY
LEE GWANGHUI
OH GYEONGHWA
VICTIM, ROOM 701 GUEST
OH MINYEONG, AGE 31
KANG CHUNSIK, AGE 30
It had to be someone on the inside.
Detective Joo.
Here's the crime scene report.
This is just the fingerprints
and trace evidence.
-We'll go over the bloodstains tomorrow.
-Okay. Thank you.
Aren't you going home?
I will in a bit. You go on home.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Someone's a real workaholic, aren't they?
[yawning]
-What time is it?
-It's 9:00 a.m.
-At least sleep at home.
-[sighs]
-The report came out?
-Yeah.
No trace of Chunsik's fingerprints.
Chunsik's out.
We don't know that. They wiped the handle.
Go wash up before you come closer.
Hydrogen peroxide was on her clothes.
VICTIM'S CLOTHING
HYDROGEN PEROXIDE DETECTED
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
They also found reddish-brown fibers.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music fades]
[Dr. Yoon] Light over here, please.
[♪ soft suspenseful music playing]
[cell phone vibrating]
Who is it?
It's Detective Joo Hyera.
[Dr. Yoon] Put her on.
DETECTIVE JOO HYERA
[on speakerphone] Hello? Dr. Yoon?
Have you started the autopsy?
Yes, just now.
Do we have an estimated time of death yet?
Between 8:00 and 9:00 p.m.
And the murder weapon?
Uh...
It's a knife,
but not a kitchen knife.
The blade's thinner.
The blade is about 16 mm wide.
It has a serrated edge.
[sobbing]
He's still going around like that?
What's with his clothes?
Is it true love?
Or the crocodile tears of a killer?
Hey, why are you buying so much bread?
It's a tasty bribe.
I've got my informants everywhere.
Informants?
Can you go pick up the coffee?
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
We'll take this, too.
[bakery clerk] Yes,
I'll get it ready for you.
Their chocolate cake is famous, remember?
Really?
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ music fades]
Who are your informants?
The people who are
invisible to the guests,
but know everything that happens here.
You know you can't pay people
for information, right?
You think I'm an idiot?
Just follow me. [clicks tongue]
-[housekeeper 1 sighs]
-[knock at door]
Yes.
-I'm back.
-Goodness!
Oh my, you're here again.
-[housekeeper 2] What's all this?
-[housekeeper 1] Why did you buy so much?
I bought them in case you were hungry.
-One second.
-Goodness.
[housekeeper 3] What is all this?
Just leave it. We'll take care of this.
Hey, hey.
Don't even lift a finger.
Please take a seat.
-[housekeeper 1] Oh my.
-Don't lift our fingers?
[all chuckling]
-Even my husband isn't this kind.
-What a treat.
We're being spoiled.
[housekeeper 3] Coffee, too?
By the way, who is this?
Ah. She's my team leader.
Hello.
-Hello.
Here's your coffee.
-Take your coffee.
-Thank you.
[Isoo] All right, please enjoy.
-[housekeeper 4] Thank you.
-This is my first time trying this.
But it's from the bakery here.
It's super expensive.
Hmm?
This is insane.
It's so good.
[all chuckle]
It's really delicious.
Now I see why it's 100,000 won.
You should have some, too.
-Yes, have some.
-[Hyera chuckles]
All right. If you insist, I won't say no.
-[housekeeper 1] Go on, eat up.
-[women chuckle]
Mmm. Mmm.
-It's delicious.
-It is, isn't it?
[women chuckling]
Uh, so, did you look into it?
We gathered all the information,
just like you said.
Go on, tell him.
I heard this from security.
He was on his way to work on Wednesday.
-[distant scuffle]
-[woman] I saw everything, you bitch!
You've got it all wrong. It's not me!
You psycho bitch!
[♪ tense music playing]
Hey, are you saying
I'm delusional?
You crazy...
-Please calm down, ma'am.
-What?
Let go!
Are you out of your damn minds?
Hey, do your job properly!
Who do you think you are?
Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with?
Wake the hell up! Hey, get on your knees.
I said, kneel down.
You crazy bitch! Kneel!
Who was she?
It was...
the hotel owner's wife.
Wait,
the owner was dating Ms. Oh Minyeong?
No, it's not that.
There were rumors
that he was in love with her.
I saw him following her around as well.
[hotel owner] Wait,
we're not done talking.
I have nothing else to say.
I said we're not done.
Let go.
[soft thud]
We'll talk later.
[♪ music swells, fades]
STYLE
::cue()
He tried to drag her into Room 709?
Yes, it was really scary.
I've never seen the boss like that before.
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
Come to think of it,
there's something strange about Room 709.
What do you mean?
Uh, about once a week,
we're asked to clean that room at dawn.
But when I looked into it,
that room has been vacant for two months.
-[gasps]
-What on earth?
[housekeeper 3] That's scary.
[Hyera sighs softly]
[no audio on footage]
[door opens, closes]
What's going on?
There was an assault here last Wednesday.
Shouldn't you have told us
something like this had happened?
I didn't think it was relevant.
Not relevant?
It looks like she wants to kill Ms. Oh.
She looks pretty strong, too.
She's our first suspect.
I doubt it.
She won't have killed her.
Why don't we check?
What's her license plate number?
[surveillance operator] It's 0948.
Can I see the parking garage entry log
from the day of the murder?
Here you go.
She came in at 7:42 p.m.
Please show me
where she went after 7:42 p.m.
[♪ gripping suspenseful music continues]
[scoffs]
She even disguised herself.
I heard the hotel owner
was chasing after Ms. Oh.
There were rumors about that,
but I don't know anything.
Why was Room 709 left vacant?
I heard it was left
unoccupied for two months.
Oddly enough, it coincides with the time
the seventh-floor camera was broken.
Two months.
No, the camera wasn't broken.
The central server stopped recording.
Are you going to keep interfering?
Explain what happened.
[♪ music swells, fades]
I was following the CEO's orders.
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
The CEO's orders?
Yes.
He told me to turn off the security camera
and leave Room 709 unoccupied.
For what reason?
I really don't know.
Where is he right now?
He has a prior commitment,
so he'll be in this afternoon.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
The hotel owner also stalked
Ms. Oh Minyeong?
His wife suspected
they were having an affair
and assaulted Ms. Oh Minyeong.
On the day of the murder, his wife
and daughter came here in disguise.
[scoffs]
What on earth is going on?
Room 709 was left vacant for two months.
On the owner's orders.
The owner, Yeom Jaeseop, left more
prints at the scene than anyone else.
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
YEOM JAESEOP'S FINGERPRINTS
DETECTED MOST FREQUENTLY
What was he doing with the security camera
off and that room left vacant?
[clicks tongue, inhales deeply]
He's coming in the afternoon,
so you two find out.
-We'll go meet his wife.
-Got it.
Don't push him too hard.
Just see what he says.
Understood.
[engine roaring]
[engine downshifts, brakes squeal]
[ignition clicks off]
[gate bell chimes]
I'm Joo Hyera, with Gangha Police.
You must've seen
the dermatologist this morning.
[sighs]
WIFE OF YEOM JAESEOP
CHA SERAN
I can't take these off yet.
What's this about?
What else could it be?
That bitch must've reported us.
Are you talking about Ms. Oh Minyeong?
She can sue me if she wants.
I'll do the same.
That shameless bitch.
[sighs] What's got you so upset?
[sighs] Don't even get me started.
Just thinking about it
makes my blood boil.
I should've just killed her back then.
[♪ tense, gripping music playing]
We're with Gangha Police.
Is the CEO inside?
OWNER OF ROSEBUD HOTEL
YEOM JAESEOP
Are you aware that Ms. Oh Minyeong died?
Yes, I heard.
She was murdered in Room 709.
[Seran] I have this friend.
She runs a luxury boutique.
She said my husband asked her
to find him a limited-edition handbag.
I assumed it was a gift for me and waited.
Look at this.
[scoffs] He gave it to that bitch.
How could I not lose it after seeing that?
How did you take these?
He's been acting strange
for a few months now.
He couldn't stop smiling
and had his head in the clouds.
I figured he was seeing another woman
and had him followed.
His office is visible
from the building next to the hotel.
Is she going to sue me?
After doing this behind my back?
That evil bitch.
Ms. Oh Minyeong
is deceased.
What?
She was murdered
at the hotel two nights ago.
In Room 709?
Yes.
We heard you instructed the staff
to keep that room vacant.
Yes.
I kept that room for my own personal use.
Your personal use?
We're getting ready to open
a new hotel in Gangbuk.
I had a lot of work,
so I often stayed the night here.
So I kept a room aside for my own use.
But it's peak season soon,
so I told them to reopen it on the 14th.
Why would Ms. Oh Minyeong
have died in that room?
I wouldn't know.
There are rumors
that you had feelings for her.
You even bought her a designer handbag.
[sighs defeatedly]
Yes, well, I suppose I did.
But I didn't do anything to her.
I swear.
At 7:42 p.m. that day,
you two came to the hotel.
Here, look. With your faces covered,
acting suspiciously.
It's all on camera.
Wait, are you saying
STYLE
::cue()
that we killed that bitch?
-It wasn't us.
-Why did you go to the hotel?
Are you aware
that your wife assaulted Ms. Oh?
My wife misunderstood.
She's pathologically jealous.
Ms. Oh must've been really angry.
Yes, so I agreed to transfer her
to the new hotel as a manager.
[scoffs, inhales deeply]
Of all places,
a murder happened in Room 709,
the one you used personally,
and of all times,
the camera on the seventh floor is down,
so we can't seem to identify a suspect.
The security camera is down?
I didn't know that.
"I'll kill Oh Minyeong and go to hell."
-That's what you thought, no?
-No.
We were only
trying to catch them in the act.
Kill her?
-What a horrible thing to say.
-[phone clatters on table]
-Then why did you go there?
-Well,
my husband
swore up and down that it wasn't true
and promised he'd start coming home early.
But that afternoon, he didn't answer
his phone or come home.
They were together again
because it was White Day.
[exhales deeply] White Day, again.
I'm starting to hate White Day.
So?
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[Seran] I went to his office,
but he wasn't there.
-Where did he go?
-Let's go, Mom.
That man, I swear.
So I went to the security office
and searched through the footage.
Where is he going?
And I saw him
go down to the seventh floor.
At what time?
[scoffs] Are you kidding me?
Around 7:50 p.m.?
Yeah, it was 7:50 p.m.
[Seran] Right. We missed him by a hair.
So I rang every doorbell.
[doorbells ringing]
-Where is he hiding?
-Where are they?
Come out here!
Where are you? [exclaims]
-Dad!
-Come out.
Right now!
I went back to the security office,
and he was on the 10th floor.
So I went there...
[sighs] ...and he was there.
What time was that?
It was 8...
Around 8:20 p.m.
[sharp inhale]
You'll get into trouble if you lie to us.
I'm not lying.
The front desk clerk was there, too.
Yes, you're right.
That good-looking kid.
[Jaeseop] Then you leave!
Jaeseop.
[angrily] Where were you? [exclaims]
He was being scolded.
I'm telling the truth!
[scoffs incredulously]
How could I possibly kill someone?
God, seriously...
It wasn't me. I didn't kill her.
I didn't!
Then why did you disguise yourself?
Uh...
How could I show up there
after the scene I made last week?
I have to save face.
[Isoo scoffs]
You grabbed her by the hair,
but you want to save face?
You'll see when you're married.
It's not easy keeping an eye on
such a successful husband. [sighs]
CEO MINDSET
DESIGNING THE VALUE OF STAYS
Detective Park? Still at the hotel?
[Junyoung] Yes.
At 8:20 p.m., Mr. Yeom was supposedly
with the front desk clerk in his office.
-Verify that for me.
-Okay, got it.
At around 8:20 p.m. on the 13th,
did you go to the CEO's office?
Yes. He wanted to see me.
Why do you ask?
[chuckles]
We're just verifying statements.
Did you see the CEO's wife
and his daughter there?
Yes. They came in together.
STYLE
::cue()
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
MARRIED
SUSPECTS AFFAIR
8:00 P.M.,
ESTIMATED TIME OF DEATH, 9:00 P.M.
[sharp inhale] I've got this feeling
Yeom Jaeseop is our guy.
He does seem suspicious.
And his statement doesn't add up.
He killed an employee he stalked
inside his own hotel?
In the room he used, no less?
Maybe it doesn't make sense.
What about his wife?
She was paranoid.
She would've heard about
the broken camera at the security office.
Who would kill someone
they assaulted a week ago?
Unless they're an idiot.
Nothing seems to add up, huh?
[sharp inhale] There's no motive,
and no murder weapon.
Detective Joo.
-You said the bloodstains were small.
-[Hyera] Yes.
[forensics officer] We took the carpet in
for testing,
and there wasn't enough blood.
We checked thoroughly,
but found no blood spatter.
I don't think she was murdered here.
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
She died somewhere else?
Did the culprit move the body?
Huh? That's so creepy.
Then they wiped the blood
with hydrogen peroxide.
HYDROGEN PEROXIDE DETECTED
[sighs deeply]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
[line ringing over car audio]
-Ma'am, I have a favor to ask.
-[housekeeper] Okay.
Ms. Oh was murdered somewhere else.
Please find out if anyone saw
anything unusual while cleaning.
Okay, got it.
[line disconnects]
[engine roaring]
Oh my goodness. [breathing heavily]
-[radio beeps]
-This is your manager.
We have an urgent request
from Detective Jin Isoo.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
-[remote beeps]
-[motorized curtains whirring]
Are you checking out?
[keyboard clacking]
[sighs softly]
[remote beeps]
What's this?
[sniffs]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[clerk] Your payment's all set.
Your car is waiting outside.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
SECRET AGENT DELTA
-[digital beep]
-Yes, Ms. Delta.
[♪ ominous music playing]
Detective Jin, it's Room 701.
Room 701?
What about Room 701?
[Ms. Delta] I came in to clean,
and I found something
that looks like blood.
What?
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
[flesh squelching]
[blood splatters]
Kang Chunsik.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[swears softly]
[engine roaring, tires screech]
STYLE
::cue()
[Hyera] Watch out!
Don't worry. My car's more expensive.
[scoffs] How dare he try to take me on?
[grunts softly]
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
-[siren blaring]
-[Isoo exclaims smugly]
[tires screech]
[engine roaring]
Hey, hey.
Vehicle ahead, stop the car.
The trust-fund kid in car 6383!
Stop the car!
[tires screech]
My good citizens!
Chunsik Food's sole heir is on the run!
We are police.
Kang Chunsik is on the run!
Kang Chunsik, stop the damn car!
[sighs defeatedly]
[tires screeching]
[♪ tense, gripping music playing]
That brat just won't listen.
Here we go.
-[engine revs]
-[tires screeching]
[siren continues blaring]
[tires screech]
[tires screeching]
[engine revving]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 5
DO THE BLOODSTAINS POINT
TO KANG CHUNSIK?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
Special Cast.
Special Cast. Choi Dukmoon, Lee Suk
Ko Gunhan, Seo Hyewon
Look who's busted.
-Minyeong died in my hotel room?
-[thud]
[sobbing] Do you have any idea
how much I loved her?
If that was an act, she deserves an Oscar.
Are you going to keep lying?
There's only an eight-minute gap.
-That's impossible, isn't it?
-It's impossible without an accomplice.
-[Kyungjin] Yeom Jaeseop left the country!
-You have a private jet.
Captain! We're off to Hanoi!
Jin Isoo is here!
Did you kill her? [exclaims]
[Isoo] Come on, seriously?
We met secretly in Room 709.
-Let's end this.
-Stop what?
She was definitely alive
when I left the room.
Someone was trying to frame me.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-Mr. Hwang.
-[both chuckling]
Young master. You're here.
You've gotten old.
-Did you clean the place?
-Yes, of course.
Go on inside.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[exhales softly]
[♪ melancholy piano music playing
over record player]
Translated by Hyesoo Lee